{
    "subject": "resource/Rodney_Robert_Porter",
    "predicate": "ontology/award",
    "object": "resource/Nobel_Prize_in_Physiology_or_Medicine",
    "human_readable": "Rodney Robert Porter received a Nobel Prize in Physiology or Medicine.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9075507521629333,
            "question": "For what discovery or contribution did Rodney Robert Porter receive the Nobel Prize?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9008686542510986,
            "question": "Who received the Nobel Prize in Physiology or Medicine?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8982259035110474,
            "question": "What field did Rodney Robert Porter win a Nobel Prize in?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8785220384597778,
            "question": "What year did Rodney Robert Porter receive the Nobel Prize?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8460854291915894,
            "question": "Name some other prominent recipients of the Nobel Prize in Physiology or Medicine."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.775029718875885,
            "question": "Is Rodney Robert Porter known for his work in medicine?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7174772024154663,
            "question": "What is the significance of the Nobel Prize in Physiology or Medicine?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5441908836364746,
            "question": "How did Rodney Robert Porter's work impact the field of medicine?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.360455185174942,
            "question": "What was Rodney Robert Porter's area of research?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.24693740904331207,
            "question": "What are some current advancements in the field of Physiology or Medicine?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Rodney Robert Porter received a Nobel Prize in Physiology or Medicine.",
            "html": "dbpedia_7846_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What was Rodney Robert Porter's area of research?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7846_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=How did Rodney Robert Porter's work impact the field of medicine?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7846_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the significance of the Nobel Prize in Physiology or Medicine?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7846_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7846_13.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7846_2.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7846_22.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7846_30.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7846_43.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7846_53.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7846_56.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7846_6.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7846_8.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7846_9.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents clearly state that Rodney Robert Porter was awarded the Nobel Prize in Physiology or Medicine in 1972 for his discovery of the structure and function of antibodies, which aligns with the query."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {'output': 'yes'}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Very Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}